badgirlsbible.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting this web site (BadGirlsBible.com). We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this web site. Please read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## Who we are

We are the Bad Girls Bible, a website dedicated to improving your sex life and relationship. Our website address is: http://badgirlsbible.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: [https://automattic.com/privacy](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

We use contact forms to collect names & email addresses from users who wish to opt in to receive our email newsletter. If you wish to unsubscribe from our email newsletter, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email from us.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Upon your initial visit to the site, we set up several cookies so that you are served more relevant content on subsequent visits.

Upon your initial visit to the site, we set up a cookie to ensure you infrequently see our pop up box with information on how to subscribe to our email newsletter and do not get bombarded with it on every page load.

Upon your initial visit to the site, we set up a cookie to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address and apply security settings on a per-client basis.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging and useful content.

You can find a list of the cookies Google Analytics uses at:

<https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage>.

You can read Google Analytics’ privacy policy and other data policies here:

<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>

If you would like to opt out of Google Analytics tracking, we recommend installing this browser plugin:

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

## Who we share your data with

We process and access the data we collect from you. However, we use third parties to assist us with processing your personal data including the following categories of recipients:

Financial transaction processors (processing your payments) – These are Clickbank and PayPal. You will find their privacy policies here:

<https://support.clickbank.com/hc/en-us/articles/360004023572-Customer-Privacy-Policy>

<https://www.paypal.com/ie/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

Survey platform – Survey Monkey. You will find their privacy policy here:

<https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/>

Email newsletter & communication manager – Aweber. You will find their privacy policy here:

<https://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm>

Marketing funnel & social media button provider – Sumo. You will find their privacy policy here:

<https://help.sumo.com/hc/en-us/articles/218958727-Privacy-Policy>

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

For users that visit the site, we will retain the Google Analytics user data associated with your visit indefinitely.

For users that purchase a product on the site, we will retain the user data associated with that purchase indefinitely.

For users that complete a survey through on our survey platform provider, we will retain the user data associated with that survey response indefinitely.

For users that opt in to our email newsletter, we will retain the user data associated with your subscriber profile indefinitely while you are active. When you become inactive for 6 months, your user data and subscriber profile will be deleted.

For users that enter our marketing funnel or use our social media buttons, we will retain the user data associated with them indefinitely.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, or have opted in to our email newsletter, or have made a purchase on the site, or have completed one of our surveys, or have entered our marketing funnel, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us.

You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you by sending an email to [sean@badgirlsbible.com](mailto:sean@badgirlsbible.com). This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. Payment data is sent to our financial transaction processor. Survey responses are sent to our survey platform. When you opt in to our email newsletter, your name and email is sent to our email newsletter & communication manager. When you enter our marketing funnel by entering your email, your email is sent to our marketing funnel & social media button provider.

## Our contact information

Contact us at:

Email is best – [sean@badgirlsbible.com](mailto:sean@badgirlsbible.com)

You can also send us snail mail to the following address:

Bad Girls Bible

Office 235

35 Upper Rathmines Road

Dublin 6

D06 X9P2

IRELAND
